

I have published eleven papers, including seven in Q1 journals in top-tier venues such as TDSC, and one in a B-ranked conference. I have mentored students to publish a high-impact paper and contributed to an Elsevier book chapter. I have received multiple awards for academic excellence, secured a successful grant application, and won an international prize. My teaching roles have been highly rated, with positive feedback from students. I also have extensive experience working with industry partners. Additionally, I hold professional certificates across multiple domains.

WORK EXPERIENCE Research statement

12.2024 – PRESENT VIN UNIVERSITY (VIET NAM)

ASSISTANT PROFESSOR (COMPUTER SCIENCE)

 Teaching: Develop curricula, instruct in cybersecurity, cryptography, networks; supervise students. Research: Publish cybersecurity work, secure funding, collaborate across disciplines.

2.2022 – 11.2024 DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)

A. RESEARCH FELLOW & RESEACH/TEACHING ASSISTANT

• Worked on publications for multiple projects in Quantum Cryptography in Virtual Private Network, AI technology (machine learning models) and cybersecurity (IoT, IDS...). Taught three subjects in cybersecurity.

8.2017 – 2.2018 TECH JDI (VIET NAM)

SENIOR TEST ENGINEER

• Delivered V-key platform, resulting in savings of 98K €.

3.2013 – 2.2017 TMA SOLUTIONS (VIET NAM)

TEST ANALYST & NETWORKING SPECIALIST

• Designed and executed test scenarios, test cases, and automated test scripts. Set up and configured the network topology for lab.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Professional certificates

10.2020 – 6.2024 DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)

DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY (CYBERSECURITY)

 <u>Award</u>: School of Information Technology 2022 Student Excellence Award Higher Degree Research.

7.2018 – 7.2020 QUEENSLAND UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY (AUSTRALIA)

MASTER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (NETWORKS)

• <u>Award</u>: Awarded Dean's List for excellent academic performance in semester 2 in 2019 and semester 1 in 2020.

9.2006 – 2.2011 PTIT (VIET NAM)

BACHELOR OF TELECOMMUNICATION & ELECTRONIC

TEACHING EXPERIENCES (DEAKIN UNIVERSITY) Teaching statement

- Deakin University: Cyber Security Management (<u>Satisfaction 100%</u> from students, <u>More</u>). Cyber Security Analytics (<u>Satisfaction 100%</u> from students). Advanced Network Security (<u>Satisfaction 92.9%</u> from students).
- VinUniversity: Cyber Security, Cryptography.

INTERNATIONAL PRIZE

I have received <u>Third Place</u> in the 2022 <u>Country to Country (C2C) Cybersecurity</u> Challenge hosted by MIT, recognizing my skills in an international cybersecurity competition.

PUBLICATIONS & MENTORSHIP

Visit my <u>Google Scholar Profile</u> and <u>IEEE Profile</u> for a complete list of publications (9 papers). I have mentored students to publish a high-impact paper (<u>IEEE TNSM</u>) and another student to publish an Elsevier book chapter (preliminary acceptance).

CONTACT

Email: ndducnha@gmail.com Phone: (+84) 0369 7777 13 https://ndducnha.github.io/my-website/